Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 21)
(الحلقة 21)
Have you ever regretted...
هل ندمت يوما على...؟
following me?
تتبعني؟
Never.
أبداً.
Xue Er.
شيويه إيه.
Xue Er, do not be afraid.
شيو إير، لا تخافي.
I will be with you soon.
سوف أكون معك قريبا.
Xue Er.
شيويه إيه.
In the next life,
في الحياة القادمة،
do not meet someone like me again.
لا تقابل شخصًا مثلي مرة أخرى.
(Xuntian Sect)
(طائفة شونتيان)
Chief.
رئيس.
Situ Xian escaped last night.
هرب سيتو شيان الليلة الماضية.
Escaped?
هربت؟
Where could he have gone?
أين كان من الممكن أن يذهب؟
He seems...
يبدو أنه...
to have gone towards the Song residence.
أن يذهب نحو مقر إقامة سونغ.
The residence of the traitor Song Lou?
محل إقامة الخائن سونغ لو؟
Yes.
نعم.
But no one has lived there for ages.
ولكن لم يعش أحد هناك منذ زمن طويل.
I do not know what he is doing there.
لا أعلم ماذا يفعل هناك.
He could not have escaped on his own.
لم يكن بإمكانه الهروب بمفرده.
Someone must have helped him escape.
لا بد أن يكون هناك شخص ساعده على الهروب.
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
Situ Xing Yuan?
الموقع شينغ يوان؟
I was worried I could not catch him,
كنت قلقًا من أنني لن أتمكن من الإمساك به،
and he handed me such a weakness himself.
وقد أعطاني مثل هذا الضعف بنفسه.
Hey, you have not recovered yet. I will go with you.
مهلا، لم تتعافى بعد. سأذهب معك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Take care of Lu Zhao.
اعتني بـلو تشاو.
Yes.
نعم.
(Song Residence)
(سكن سونغ)
I have been waiting for you.
لقد كنت في انتظارك.
Situ Xing Yuan let you out, right?
سيتو شينغ يوان سمح لك بالخروج، أليس كذلك؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
If it were not for you and Xiao Jin Yu,
إذا لم يكن الأمر لك ولشياو جين يو،
Xue Er would not have died!
شيو إير لن يموت!
If it were not for you and Lu Zhao,
لو لم يكن الأمر لك ولو تشاو،
I would have already ascended...
لقد صعدت بالفعل...
the supreme throne...
العرش الأعلى...
and commanded a realm of thousands of miles.
وحكم مملكة تمتد لآلاف الأميال.
You all ruined everything.
لقد دمرتم كل شيء.
Today,
اليوم،
I will put an end to this once and for all.
سأضع حدا لهذا الأمر مرة واحدة وإلى الأبد.
Your good uncle is set on getting the Imperial Palace Defense Map.
عمك الصالح عازم على الحصول على خريطة دفاع القصر الإمبراطوري.
How could he let me die?
كيف يمكنه أن يتركني أموت؟
He must have already tampered with your gunpowder.
لا بد أنه قد تلاعب بالبارود الخاص بك بالفعل.
Situ Xian.
الموقع شيان.
Think about...
فكر في...
every single incident that has transpired in the past.
كل حادثة وقعت في الماضي.
Who was it that orchestrated...
من هو الذي قام بتدبير...؟
your marriage to Lu Zhao?
زواجك من لو تشاو؟
And who bewitched you...
ومن سحرك...
to use the Lu family's wealth...
لإستغلال ثروة عائلة لو...
for illicit arms dealing and collusion with the Qiang?
بتهمة الاتجار غير المشروع بالأسلحة والتواطؤ مع تشيانغ؟
And now, for whose sake...
والآن من أجل من...
are you taking on these crimes?
هل تتولى هذه الجرائم؟
And who...
ومن...
used you as bait today...
لقد استخدمتك كطعم اليوم...
just to lure me here?
فقط لإغرائي هنا؟
Situ Xian,
سيتو شيان,
you have been a pawn all your life,
لقد كنت مجرد بيدق طوال حياتك،
at the mercy of others.
على رحمة الآخرين.
Do not let him control you anymore.
لا تسمحي له بالسيطرة عليك بعد الآن.
Tell me where he is.
أخبرني أين هو؟
I will not kill you.
لن اقتلك
Using?
استخدام؟
By telling me all this now,
بإخباري بكل هذا الآن،
are you not also using me?
هل أنت لا تستخدمني أيضًا؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know everything.
انا اعرف كل شئ
All of you...
جميعكم...
All of you are using me.
أنتم جميعا تستخدمونني.
I, Situ Xian,
أنا، سيتو شيان،
an imperial scion,
سليل إمبراطوري،
was dragged down by my own birth mother.
لقد تم جرّي إلى أسفل بواسطة والدتي الحقيقية.
My whole life was burdened by my origins,
لقد كانت حياتي كلها مثقلة بأصولي،
trapped in a game of chess.
عالق في لعبة الشطرنج.
All who treated me sincerely...
كل من عاملني بصدق...
were betrayed by me.
لقد خانوني.
And now,
والآن،
I am ensnared in the cocoon I spun,
لقد وقعت في فخ الشرنقة التي نسجتها،
foolish beyond measure.
أحمق إلى أبعد الحدود.
I am coming to find you.
أنا قادم للبحث عنك.
(Song)
(أغنية)
Master Xiao.
المعلم شياو.
Look at the Song family crest.
أنظر إلى شعار عائلة سونغ.
Does it not resemble the symbol on the jade pendant?
هل لا يشبه الرمز الموجود على قلادة اليشم؟
Situ Xing Yuan.
الموقع شينغ يوان.
You dare come to see me alone?
هل تجرؤ على المجيء لرؤيتي بمفردك؟
Master Xiao,
السيد شياو،
you have been a part of the Xiao family for so long.
لقد كنت جزءًا من عائلة شياو لفترة طويلة.
Do you not want to know...
هل لا تريد أن تعرف...
who your biological parents are?
من هم والدك البيولوجيين؟
I...
أنا...
just want to tell you...
فقط أريد أن أخبرك...
who you really are.
من أنت حقا.
(Song Family Genealogy)
(علم الأنساب لعائلة سونغ)
Back then, Song Lou committed treason,
في ذلك الوقت، ارتكب سونغ لو الخيانة،
causing my younger sister to die tragically in Northern Qiang.
مما تسبب في وفاة أختي الصغرى بشكل مأساوي في شمال تشيانغ.
The Emperor sentenced his entire family to be executed.
حكم الإمبراطور على عائلته بأكملها بالإعدام.
The entire Song family,
عائلة سونغ بأكملها،
to preserve their dignity,
للحفاظ على كرامتهم،
hanged themselves...
شنقوا أنفسهم...
the night before the execution.
الليلة السابقة للإعدام.
When I arrived,
عندما وصلت،
only the child in Lady Song's womb...
فقط الطفل في رحم السيدة سونغ...
and the heirloom jade pendant...
والقلادة اليشمية التذكارية...
had vanished.
قد اختفى.
That is to say,
وهذا يعني،
you are a descendant of the Song family.
أنت من نسل عائلة سونغ.
Do you think...
هل تعتقد...
a fake genealogy book...
كتاب أنساب مزيف...
can fool me?
هل يستطيع أن يخدعني؟
The Song Lou case caused a stir.
أثارت قضية سونغ لو ضجة كبيرة.
His Majesty was furious.
وكان جلالته غاضبا.
The Three Judicial Offices held a joint trial.
عقدت الهيئات القضائية الثلاث محاكمة مشتركة.
A genealogy book can be forged,
يمكن تزوير كتاب الأنساب،
but the official case files...
لكن ملفات القضية الرسمية...
could never be falsified.
لا يمكن تزويرها أبدًا.
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
Jin Lin will immediately...
جين لين سوف يقوم على الفور...
expose your background.
كشف خلفيتك.
Do you dare to bet with me?
هل تجرؤ على الرهان معي؟
Xiao Ren,
شياو رن,
you dare not kill me.
لا تجرؤ على قتلي.
Because you are afraid.
لأنك خائفة.
You know the Song family and the Xiao family are blood enemies.
أنت تعرف أن عائلة سونغ وعائلة شياو أعداء بالدم.
You are afraid that if your background is exposed,
أنت خائف من أنه إذا تم الكشف عن خلفيتك،
Xiao Jin Yu will hate you to the bone,
شياو جين يو سوف يكرهك حتى العظم،
crush your bones, and scatter your ashes.
اسحق عظامك، وانثر رمادك.
All that you desire in life...
كل ما تتمناه في الحياة...
will turn to dust.
سوف يتحول إلى غبار.
As for growing old together in harmony,
أما بالنسبة للتقدم في السن معًا في وئام،
that is just a pipe dream.
هذا مجرد حلم بعيد المنال.
I was born and raised in the Xiao family.
لقد ولدت ونشأت في عائلة شياو.
The blood flowing in my veins...
الدم يتدفق في عروقي...
is that of the Xiao family.
هي عائلة شياو.
I am not a Song!
أنا لست أغنية!
Look closely.
أنظر عن كثب.
You are a Song.
أنت أغنية.
The blood of the Song family runs in your veins.
دماء عائلة سونغ تجري في عروقك.
Once His Majesty learns of this,
وبمجرد أن يعلم جلالته بهذا الأمر،
the entire Xiao family will be implicated.
سيتم إشراك عائلة شياو بأكملها .
This is...
هذا هو...
a dead end.
طريق مسدود.
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
Give me the Imperial Palace Defense Map.
أعطني خريطة دفاع القصر الإمبراطوري.
I will keep your true identity a secret forever.
سأبقي هويتك الحقيقية سرية إلى الأبد.
You want me to commit treason?
هل تريدني أن أرتكب الخيانة؟
Ninth Prince,
الأمير التاسع
you are wrong.
أنت مخطئ.
I have another solution.
لدي حل آخر.
Have you forgotten?
هل نسيت؟
I am a Xiao.
انا شياو.
We, the Xiao family, would...
نحن، عائلة شياو، نود...
rather...
بدلاً من...
die...
ال...
than...
من...
betray.
خيانة.
Betray the country?
خيانة الوطن؟
No.
لا.
My sister was tortured to death by the Qiang people.
لقد تعرضت أختي للتعذيب حتى الموت على يد شعب تشيانغ.
I have a blood feud with the Qiang.
لدي ثأر دم مع تشيانغ.
I would never commit treason for glory.
لن أرتكب الخيانة من أجل المجد أبدًا.
If I ascend the throne,
إذا صعدت إلى العرش،
I will never allow Southern Qing to be humiliated.
لن أسمح أبدًا بإذلال جنوب تشينغ.
I will fight with the Qiang kingdom to the bitter end.
سأقاتل مملكة تشيانغ حتى النهاية المريرة.
In fact, I have already made all the necessary preparations.
في الواقع، لقد قمت بالفعل بكل التحضيرات اللازمة.
I can purge the palace with blood and ascend the throne at any time.
أستطيع تطهير القصر بالدم واعتلاء العرش في أي وقت.
The reason I want the Imperial Palace Defense Map...
السبب الذي يجعلني أريد خريطة دفاع القصر الإمبراطوري...
is simply to avoid harming innocent lives.
الهدف هو ببساطة تجنب إيذاء أرواح الأبرياء.
What have the palace guards done wrong?
ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبه حراس القصر ؟
What have the people of the capital done wrong?
ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبه سكان العاصمة؟
A foolish emperor sits on the throne.
إمبراطور أحمق يجلس على العرش.
Your identity exposed.
تم الكشف عن هويتك.
Innocent people slain.
قتل الأبرياء.
Is this the outcome you want?
هل هذه هي النتيجة التي تريدها؟
I promise you,
أعدك،
I will never slaughter the innocent.
لن أذبح الأبرياء أبدًا.
And I will treat the former emperor well,
وسأعامل الإمبراطور السابق بشكل جيد،
allowing him to live out his days as the Taishang Huang.
السماح له بالعيش بقية أيامه باعتباره تايشانغ هوانغ.
I will also...
انا سوف افعل ايضا...
personally issue a decree...
أصدر شخصيا مرسوما...
to bestow marriage upon you and Lu Zhao.
أن أمنحك الزواج من لو تشاو.
This collaboration...
هذا التعاون...
will benefit you,
سوف تستفيد
me,
أنا،
and the people of the world.
وشعوب العالم.
It brings only benefits, without a single harm.
فهو لا يجلب إلا المنافع، دون أي ضرر.
I will give you time to consider.
سأعطيك الوقت للتفكير.
You are a smart person.
أنت شخص ذكي.
You know how to choose.
أنت تعرف كيف تختار.
Situ Xian...
سيتو شيان...
is my token of sincerity to you.
إنها علامة صدقي لك.
I hope you will show your sincerity as well.
أتمنى أن تظهر صدقك أيضًا.
Do not disappoint me.
لا تخيب ظني.
(Case Files Archive)
(أرشيف ملفات القضايا)
(Song Lou Treason Case)
(قضية خيانة سونغ لو)
In the ninth year of Shuntai,
في السنة التاسعة من شونتاي،
Song Lou committed treason.
ارتكب سونغ لو الخيانة.
His family was executed and nearly wiped out.
لقد تم إعدام عائلته وكادوا أن يبادوا بالكامل.
However, the Song family's newborn heir...
ومع ذلك، فإن وريث عائلة سونغ حديث الولادة...
and the Song family heirloom jade...
وإرث عائلة سونغ من اليشم...
were secretly sent away by Lady Song...
تم إرسالهم سرا من قبل السيدة سونغ...
and disappeared without a trace.
واختفى دون أن يترك أثرا.
(Song)
(أغنية)
How utterly ridiculous.
كم هو سخيف تماما.